LUIS ROCHA: DESIGN-MINDED WEB DEVELOPER.

<u>luisrochadev.com</u> <u>luisrochaphoto.com</u> <u>luisrochadev@gmail.com</u> (619) 699-9854

SUMMARY

Frontend web developer with a passion for design. Skilled in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Angular. Proficient with the Adobe Creative Suite. Obsessed with producing intuitive and aesthetically pleasing user experiences. Clean, responsive, mobile-first design above all else. I am always learning.

SKILLS

Front-end development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
Front-end frameworks & libraries (Angular, Bootstrap, jQuery, SASS, WordPress)
Back-end development (Node.JS, Express)

Testing & deployment (Mocha, Heroku) Tools (Git, GitHub, Bitbucket, NPM)

Adobe Creative Suite (PS, Lightroom, InDesign, etc)

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER - Interact Intranet

June 2016 - October 2016

Used WordPress to build and update all public facing web pages, landing pages, and marketing pages with conversion optimization in mind. Analyzed UI/UX of existing pages to ensure fully responsive, cross-browser usability. Maintained efficient front-end performance and top 10 SEO keyword ranking.

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER - San Franpsycho Clothing

December 2014 - September 2015

Increased social media follower count by 40% and customer engagement by 60% in the span of 6 months. Developed new social media strategy to stimulate brand growth and increase sales. Managed published content (images, video and written).

STAFF PHOTOGRAPHER - San Franpsycho Clothing

August 2013 - September 2015

Established brand's visual aesthetic and identity. Worked closely with executive team and designers to conceptualize photoshoots and lookbooks. Prioritized multiple projects to ensure all deadlines were consistently met.

FOUNDER, PHOTOGRAPHER: Luis Rocha Photography

January 2011 - Present

Self-employed freelancer. Proactively sought out clients and secured contracts with major brands and music festivals including Outside Lands, Coachella, EDC, and more. Created batch-editing scripts to quickly edit large volumes of photos. Established online presence through several social media channels.

EDUCATION

GALVANIZE San Francisco, CA 24-Week Web Development Program

SAN FRANCISCO STATE UNIVERSITY San Francisco, CA

Business Administration - Marketing